MRS. KOOTHRAPPALI: What are we
supposed to say to Lalita's parents?
(Dr Koothrappali:)I play golf with her father.
I won't be able to look at him.
(Raj:)Maybe you should keep
your eye on the ball, Papa.
Oh, now you're a funnyman?
This is not funny, Mr. Funnyman.
Dr. and Mrs. Koothrappali, in all fairness,
it wasn't entirely Raj's fault.
- This is a family matter, Sheldon.
- No, I'm Leonard.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Oh. Sorry. You all look alike to us.
(Raj:)But he's right, Papa. Listen to him.
[DOOR OPENS]
You, you are the one
who ruined everything.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Who is it? We can't see.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Turn us. Turn us.
(Raj:)Go ahead, tell my parents why
they won't have any grandchildren.
How would I know?
Do you have a low sperm count?
(Raj:)This has nothing to do
with my sperm count.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)You are wearing the boxers
that we sent you, aren't you?
(Raj:)Yes, Mommy.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)You know what happens to the samosas
when you wear the tighty whities.
(Raj:)Can we please stop talking
about my testicles?
(Raj:)- Sheldon, tell them what you did.
- What did I do?